Guide to the Cornell University Corporate and Foundation Relations records, 1968-1986.
Cornell University Corporate and Foundation Relations records, 1968-1986
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell University Corporate and Foundation Relations records, 1968-1986.
4-3-2538
Cornell University. University Development. Corporate and Foundation Relations.
8 cubic ft.
Correspondence, corporate records.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence and other documents relating to Cornell's interaction with corporations and foundations outside the University.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence and other documents relating to Cornell's interaction with corporations and foundations outside the University.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University. University Development. Corporate and Foundation Relations.; Cornell University--Public relations.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted to permission of office of origin.
CONTAINER LIST
- Amoco, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Atlantic Richfield, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- AT&T, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- AT&T, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Chemical Bank (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Chevron, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 6-7)
- Corning Glass, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Digital Equipment, 1983-1985 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Dow Chemical, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- DuPont, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 11-12)
- Eastman Kodak, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Emerson Electric, 1982-1984 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Exxon, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 15-17)
- General Electric, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 18-21)
- General Foods, 1981-1985 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- General Motors, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Heinz, H.J., 1984 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Hewlett-Packard, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 1-2)
- IBM, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 3-5)
- Dart Kraft, 1982-1985 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Merck, 1982-1985 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Monsanto, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Mobil Oil, 1984-1986 (Box 2, Folder 9-10)
- National Cash Register, 1982-1985 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Procter & Gamble, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Pfizer, 1984-1986 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- RJR Nabisco, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Rohm & Haas, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Signal Companies, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Shell Oil, 1984-1986 (Box 2, Folder 17-20)
- Schlumberger, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Standard Oil (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Sun Oil, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 23-25)
- TRW, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Unisys, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Union Carbide, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Varian Associates, 1982-1986 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Xerox, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 30-31)
- Carnegie Corporation, 1975-1980 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Clark (Edna McConnell) Foundation, 1969-1972 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Dana Foundation, 1965-1985 (Box 3, Folder 3-4)
- Davis (Arthur Vining) Foundation, 1976-1981 (Box 3, Folder 5-7)
- Dodge (Geraldine R.) Foundation, 1973-1981 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Exxon Education Foundation, 1977-1984 (Box 3, Folder 9-12)
- Ford Foundation, 1970-1984 (Box 3, Folder 13-18)
- Gannett Foundation, 1980-1982 (Box 4, Folder 1-3)
- Hazen (Edward W.) Foundation (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Hewlett Foundation, 1977-1985 (Box 4, Folder 5-10)
- Hilton (Conrad N.) Foundation (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Keck Foundation, 1981-1983 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Kellogg Foundation, 1977-1986 (Box 4, Folder 13-18)
- Kettering Family Foundation (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Kresge Foundation, 1974-1982 (Box 5, Folder 2-5)
- Kress Foundation, 1975-1986 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- MacArthur (John D. and Catherine T.) Foundation (Box 5, Folder 7-9)
- Mellon (Andrew W.) Foundation, 1977-1982 (Box 5, Folder 10-16)
- Mellon (Andrew W.) Foundation, 1974-1980 (Box 6, Folder 1-3)
- Noyes (Jessie Smith) Foundation, 1977-1982 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- O'Connor Foundation, 1970-1983 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Pew Charitable Trusts (Box 6, Folder 6-17)
- Pew Charitable Trusts (Box 7, Folder 1-10)
- Phillips Foundation, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 11-12)
- Revson Foundation (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Rockefeller Foundation, 1964-1982 (Box 7, Folder 14-16)
- Sicca (Michele) Trust (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Sloan Foundation, 1972-1981 (Box 7, Folder 18-20)
- Snow (John Ben) Foundation, 1976-1984 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Spencer Foundation, 1975-1981 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Surdna Foundation, 1968-1982 (Box 8, Folder 3-5)
- Teagle Foundation, 1963-1981 (Box 8, Folder 6-8)